<jobs><job><job_title>Machine Learning Scientist - Applied</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;t integrate.ai, our mission is to power a new intelligence ecosystem that is built on trust and mutual benefit for people and organizations. To do this we are building an AI powered platform for B2C enterprises that integrates with business processes to make client interactions more natural, meaningful, and valuable. We are proudly based in downtown Toronto, Canada at the center of an exciting AI ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We are looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning Scientist (Applied)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; who is excited to play an integral part of a client facing team, who excels at uncovering concise business insights, and who can both deliver and communicate these insights effectively to external stakeholders. Responsibilities for this role range from data ingestion to collaborating with both internal and external stakeholders to build the platform in a way that best suits our client&#8217;s needs.&#160; This is a fascinating role that requires both strong interpersonal skills and deep technical knowledge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Using your data science superpowers to advise clients on everything from use case development to solution design to performance measurement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Collaborating with other Machine Learning Scientists on the team to problem-solve and develop best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Principally delivering data ingest for our client data, including cataloguing the data and mapping it to our proprietary data schema&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Collaborating with our business team to create polished data visualizations and pull high level business insights from client data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Working closely with our machine learning research team in the early stages of statistical/machine learning model development to identify valuable patterns and information in the data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Collaborating with our engineers to translate complex business logic into our proprietary data schema&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Supporting engineers to do carry out reliable and efficient integrations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Sending feedback to our engineering, product, and machine learning research teams to develop requirements for our product roadmap - specifically our ingest, structuring, and integration capabilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;5+ years in a lead Machine Learning (or Data) Science role, including experience providing strategic guidance to clients and fellow Machine Learning (or Data) Scientists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;An appreciation for the beauty of data. You love a challenge, and you&#8217;re excited about bringing a narrative to complex business problems using what you learn from a dataset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Worked directly with clients and understand the importance of prioritizing client needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science or a related discipline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Strong technical abilities, creative problem solving skills and high adaptability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Extraordinary interpersonal, organization and communications skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Experience working directly with business users to build reports and answer business questions with data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Experience working with big data structures and ETL tools and other big data technologies (Hadoop/Spark, Hive SQL, etc.) to uncover meaningful business insights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A strong understanding of statistical modeling and you&#8217;re passionate about deriving insights from large datasets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Programming experience with Python, R, or SAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Adaptability and interest in working with a dynamic, early stage company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The diverse experiences, ideas, and identities of integrate.ai&#8217;s team members helps us make better decisions and drive great results.&#160; We foster an inclusive work environment that welcomes team members of all backgrounds and perspectives. We\'re committed to providing a meaningful environment for every member of our team.&#160; We hire exceptional people and reward them with trust, autonomy, mentorship, and growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We are naturally curious and have strong attention to detail. We love working in a team environment where trust is key and we all strive to make an impact every day. If this sounds like the right fit, please apply and come work with us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://boards.greenhouse.io/integrateai/jobs/4220487002</url><apply_email /><job_img>https://s2-recruiting.cdn.greenhouse.io/external_greenhouse_job_boards/logos/400/504/600/resized/Copy_of_Social_image_for_website_sharing_-_Logo.png?1572450267</job_img><company>integrate.ai</company><company_url>https://integrate.ai/</company_url><city>Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Software Engineer (Platform)</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;At&lt;strong&gt;&#160;integrate.ai&lt;/strong&gt;, our mission is to build a future in which AI enriches people&#8217;s lives while creating better, more valuable businesses. &#160;We are looking for extraordinary people to help build our AI-powered platform which helps B2C enterprises become more customer-centric, identifying what customers value in businesses and applying AI to guide them to unique experiences. &#160;We care about privacy and ethics and are working to make Responsible AI a reality across consumer enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an incredible &lt;strong&gt;Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&#160;Engineer (Platform)&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;who is passionate about taking AI to the next level and is interested in being part of our core development team. As a Software Engineer, you will play a key role in the development of impactful features for our SaaS platform, from novel user interfaces powered by sophisticated back-end services to large scale data processing and AI training pipelines. Knowledge of machine learning techniques is not required to apply as we have a great team of experts in this area, but the role provides plenty of opportunities to learn and get up to speed should you be interested. This role will report to one of our Software Engineering Managers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, you will be surrounded by some of the most talented minds in the AI industry. Seriously, please check us out on LinkedIn!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making high-impact decisions that other developers will live with in the future: you design, develop, and deploy cutting edge technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building impactful services and features in a way that you can be proud of&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operating services at scale and with world class reliability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extending and improving your services to drive better outcomes for people&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the growth and development of your colleagues and the company&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Product Management to define services and features, and to realistically plan and estimate their complexity &#160;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building client facing and internal web applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be responsible for designing and implementing features for several large projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in infrastructure development and operations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing existing codebase and developing new products for customers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implementing integration with existing customer systems and providing support and documentation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in agile project planning and estimation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing on-demand developer support directly to clients and their partners&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We Value:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Writing great code in any language! &#160;We&#8217;re a python and react shop, but we appreciate the expertise you can bring in any language.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A degree in Computer Engineering, Computer Science or an equivalent degree or experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing large scale, distributed, web-based services and feeling both the pleasure and burden of operating these services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Delivery of impactful solutions to customers and provided their continuous support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with relational databases and SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience using 3rd party REST/RPC APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Superior understanding of CS fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of value and operational cost of delivered solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working in an agile environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with AWS/GCP infrastructure is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great desire and willingness to learn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contributions to the growth and success of your teammates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://boards.greenhouse.io/integrateai/jobs/4230507002</url><apply_email /><job_img>https://s2-recruiting.cdn.greenhouse.io/external_greenhouse_job_boards/logos/400/504/600/resized/Copy_of_Social_image_for_website_sharing_-_Logo.png?1572450267</job_img><company>integrate.ai</company><company_url>https://integrate.ai/</company_url><city>Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Machine Learning Scientist - Research</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;At integrate.ai, our mission is to power a new intelligence ecosystem that is built on trust and mutual benefit for people and organizations. To do this we are building an AI powered platform for B2C enterprises that integrates with business processes to make client interactions more natural, meaningful, and valuable. We are proudly based in downtown Toronto, Canada at the center of an exciting AI ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We are looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning Scientist (Research)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; to join our research team. This role delves into the art of the possible, and is neatly placed at the cross-section of cutting edge science and latest industry trends. It also represents a unique opportunity for someone who wants to work with a team of smart and passionate individuals committed to bringing new AI/ML products to the business enterprise world.&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Assist in shaping the research agenda by keeping abreast of latest technical developments (areas of interest include: federated learning, domain adaptation, transfer learning, reinforcement learning, causal inference, fair ML, privacy-preserving techniques.) and understanding how these can potentially impact the industries that we work in.&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Researching and developing intelligent systems (e.g., machine learning models, reinforcement learning systems) to power the platform&#8217;s scientific capabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Conduct experiments that focus on reproducibility and reliability to test out complex ideas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Present and share research findings in a clear manner through integrate.ai&#8217;s internal technical reports (and when appropriate, share these findings through external outlets such as paper publications and conference presentations).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A Masters or PhD in Machine Learning, Applied Statistics, Computer Science, or a related quantitative discipline.&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;5+ years of hands-on machine learning experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Expertise in at least one of the following areas: federated learning, transfer learning, domain adaptation, reinforcement learning, generative modelling, fair ML, causal inference, privacy-preserving techniques.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;High quality research publications and/or open-source projects&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Great proficiency in machine learning tools such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, Scikit Learn, Theano, Spark MLlib.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The diverse experiences, ideas, and identities of integrate.ai&#8217;s team members help us make better decisions and drive great results. We foster an inclusive work environment that welcomes team members of all backgrounds and perspectives. We are committed to providing a meaningful environment for every member of our team. We hire exceptional people and reward them with trust, autonomy, mentorship, and growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We are naturally curious and have strong attention to detail. We love working in a team environment where trust is key and we all strive to make an impact every day. If this sounds like the right fit, please apply and come work with us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://boards.greenhouse.io/integrateai/jobs/4224910002</url><apply_email /><job_img>https://s2-recruiting.cdn.greenhouse.io/external_greenhouse_job_boards/logos/400/504/600/resized/Copy_of_Social_image_for_website_sharing_-_Logo.png?1572450267</job_img><company>integrate.ai</company><company_url>https://integrate.ai/</company_url><city>Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Senior Product Manager</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We are looking for an incredible Senior Product Manager who is passionate about taking enterprise AI to the next level as a member of our Product and Design Team. You will be at the forefront of shaping our product and the future of how businesses use AI to drive their engagement with customers. We believe that trust and respect for privacy are the foundation of strong customer relationships and are building the next generation of AI-driven solutions that enable businesses to make the right decisions at the right time.&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;An understanding of Machine Learning and enterprise data-driven workflows will be a significant asset, but is not required. This role will report to the SVP of Product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;At&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; integrate.ai&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;, our mission is to power an intelligence ecosystem built on trust and mutual benefit for people and organizations, and to do so in a way that embeds positive human values into algorithmic decisions.&#160; We are looking for extraordinary people to help build our AI-powered platform which helps B2C enterprises become more customer-centric, identifying what customers value in businesses and applying AI to guide them to unique experiences.&#160; We care about privacy and ethics and are working to make Responsible AI a reality across consumer enterprise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Most importantly, you will be surrounded by some of the most talented minds in the AI industry. Seriously, please check us out on Linkedin!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Serve as product owner for key applications&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Lead exploration of new use cases, mapping our unique science/engineering capabilities to market opportunities, iterating quickly towards MVP and in-market testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Major contributor to product vision and roadmap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Interact with users to understand their needs and develop new opportunity hypotheses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Daily interactions with our engineering, science, design, and go-to-market teams; driving alignment around our product vision and roadmap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Stay on top of market trends, specifically related to AI in the enterprise and data applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Drive product delivery, from alpha/beta MVP through to general release maturity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Serve as a mentor to junior members of the product team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Expectations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;You thrive under the energy and ambiguity of early-stage product development, continually developing hypotheses, testing them, and iterating at a fast pace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;7+ years in a technical role, with at least 4 of those in a product management role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Strong grasp of product management fundamentals and an interest to mentor others&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Comfortable interacting with engineers and machine learning scientists, with an ability to context switch between concepts related to outward facing UI all the way to the core technology stack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Focus on shipping product and experimenting in-market with engaged early adopters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://boards.greenhouse.io/integrateai/jobs/5112976002</url><apply_email /><job_img>https://s2-recruiting.cdn.greenhouse.io/external_greenhouse_job_boards/logos/400/504/600/resized/Copy_of_Social_image_for_website_sharing_-_Logo.png?1572450267</job_img><company>integrate.ai</company><company_url>https://integrate.ai/</company_url><city>Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Sr. DevOps Engineer&#160;</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__inner"&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__intro"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will join the team in solving the challenges of developing high performance, robust and scalable machine learning solutions and delivering them in production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;world-class&lt;/span&gt; devops engineers and problem solvers.&lt;br/&gt;You will be interacting with machine learning scientists and engineers to develop and automate machine learning pipelines that work. In particular, you will participate in the development, delivery and automation of scalable systems for data ingestion, processing, validation, model training, large-scale computation, monitoring, serving results and handling upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__main"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Requirements&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Must-Have&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience building sophisticated and automated production infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid Azure or AWS experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with Kubernetes, docker and container orchestration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Saltstack or other configuration management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong scripting skills, i.e., Bash, Python, Groovy etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with managing CI/CD tools and pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong practical Linux systems administration skills in a Cloud environment, Redhat and Ubuntu&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Git, Jenkins and Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills, with the ability to work effectively across teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BA/BS degree or equivalent experience; Computer Science background preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Nice-to-Have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of IP networking, VPN&#8217;s, DNS, load balancing and firewalls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with monitoring tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with automated testing tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience troubleshooting and tuning systems performance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Java&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Benefits:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial and learning culture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent health coverage and pension plan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Four weeks paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Catered lunches twice a week over machine learning talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://layer6.ai/careers/#Sr-DevOps-Engineer-663</url><job_img>https://layer6.ai/wp-content/themes/layer6ai/assets/images/logo.svg</job_img><apply_email>careers@layer6.ai</apply_email><company>layer6</company><company_url>https://layer6.ai/</company_url><city>MaRS Discovery District at University &amp; College in Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Machine Learning Engineer &#8211; Framework</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__inner"&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__intro"&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;We are looking for world-class engineers to tackle cutting-edge problems of applying Machine Learning in the real world. Join this team to develop a framework for machine learning models that have real world impact. The goal of the framework is to help our ML Scientists build robust and high performing models through providing a solid foundation and allowing for fast iteration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Machine Learning Engineer at Layer 6, you will work with ML Scientists to learn their modelling workflow, so that you can &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;design abstractions and build components&lt;/span&gt; that can be combined to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;build high quality models.&lt;/span&gt; You will work with ML Platform team to make sure these models can be trained and deployed on our computing infrastructure, taking advantage of cloud technologies like Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__main"&gt;&lt;h4 style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;Must-Have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with building and scaling data-intensive software in Java&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You value good software design and sweat over details in code and API design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of machine learning modelling workflow&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You enjoy learning new technology and also educating others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You strive to communicate clearly and with empathy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You take great personal pride in building robust and scalable software&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are highly accountable and have a strong sense of ownership&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to do detailed code reviews and give thoughtful feedback&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;Nice to have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience building a library or a framework&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of machine learning algorithms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comfortable with math or statistics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://layer6.ai/careers/#Machine-Learning-Engineer-8211-Framework-591</url><job_img>https://layer6.ai/wp-content/themes/layer6ai/assets/images/logo.svg</job_img><apply_email>careers@layer6.ai</apply_email><company>layer6</company><company_url>https://layer6.ai/</company_url><city>MaRS Discovery District at University &amp; College in Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Sr. Machine Learning Product Engineer &#8211; Tech Lead</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__inner"&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__intro"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Machine Learning Product Engineer team at Layer 6 focuses on building industry-leading data-centric systems and model delivery systems. Our solutions include data pipelines, feature data lake, systemic data validation and automation of key activities in model delivery including model validation, shakedown, inference, and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;experienced&lt;/span&gt; Senior Machine Learning Product Engineers (Sr. MLPE) who have worked under tight deadlines and on challenging tasks. The ideal candidate is &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;a master of coding and system design&lt;/span&gt;. They also are &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;experts in data engineering and/or machine learning&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The candidate will be &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;the go-to person for data and model delivery&lt;/span&gt;. They will &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;lead and coordinate efforts of members on the MLPE team&lt;/span&gt; to ensure best engineering practice in our systems. The candidate will interact with machine learning scientists, the infrastructure team and data sources team to develop systems that will satisfy the needs of machine learning projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__main"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your main responsibilities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Lead the design and implementation of complex data-centric solutions, including extremely complex and large data set verification, transformation and feature generation, to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;ensure continuous high-quality input for the model development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Lead the design and implementation of model delivery systems, including inference pipeline, automatic model validation reports generation, automatic model performance monitoring and model retraining, to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;ensure fast model productionization and reliable production system &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;Go-to person&lt;/span&gt; for data and model delivery within Layer 6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__green"&gt;Lead and mentor&lt;/span&gt; Machine Learning Product Engineers to ensure best engineering practice in our systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Technical Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;BSc+ in Computer Science, Math, Physics, or similar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;5+ years of extensive programming experience, at least 3 years in building production data systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;3+ years experience of building machine learning production system&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Expert level skills in system design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Expert in Big Data technologies and frameworks including but not limited to Hadoop, MapReduce, Spark, Cassandra, Kafka, Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Strong knowledge of Machine Learning and Deep Learning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Practical expertise in performance tuning, bottleneck problems analysis, and troubleshooting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Experience with Big Data solutions developed in large cloud computing infrastructures such as Azure and AWS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Strong experience with Scala and Java 8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;C++, Python experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Entrepreneurial and inclusive culture&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Excellent health coverage and pension plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Four weeks paid vacation&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400"&gt;Catered lunches twice a week over machine learning talks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://layer6.ai/careers/#Sr-Machine-Learning-Product-Engineer-8211-Tech-Lead-614</url><job_img>https://layer6.ai/wp-content/themes/layer6ai/assets/images/logo.svg</job_img><apply_email>careers@layer6.ai</apply_email><company>layer6</company><company_url>https://layer6.ai/</company_url><city>MaRS Discovery District at University &amp; College in Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Machine Learning Engineer &#8211; Backend</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__inner"&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__intro"&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;We are looking for world-class engineers to tackle cutting-edge problems of applying Machine Learning in the real world. Join this team to help develop a system that will serve as the main interface to our machine learning platform. The goal of this system is to help in all stages of model development, from feature engineering all the way to production monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We empower our ML Scientists to build better models by helping them understand the data and trained models. We also provide the tools necessary for analyzing and visualizing machine learning algorithms in an effort to extract valuable business insights in a transparent and comprehensive manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;As Senior Backend Engineer at Layer 6, you&#8217;ll work with ML scientists to learn about different machine learning algorithms and ways to analyze them. On the back end, you&#8217;ll work with the team to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;architect systems and design an API &lt;/span&gt;for the front-end web application which will visualize data and answer questions about machine learning models.&#160;You&#8217;ll also have the opportunity to work with the engineering team to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;tackle the challenge of developing high performance, robust and scalable systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__main"&gt;&lt;h4 style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;Must-have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&#8211; BSc+ in Computer Science or similar&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; 3+ years of programming experience&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Proven experience in designing and delivering a complex web application&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Experience as a key contributor and leader on projects&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Strong experience in Java and its ecosystem&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Passionate about creating maintainable and performant software&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Strong desire to learn and solve problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;Nice to have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="font-weight: 400"&gt;&#8211; Experience with databases such as Elasticsearch&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Experience with microservice architecture&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Familiarity with data analysis or machine learning&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Experience with Docker and Kubernetes&lt;br/&gt;&#8211; Comfortable with math (linear algebra, calculus)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://layer6.ai/careers/#Machine-Learning-Engineer-8211-Backend-617</url><job_img>https://layer6.ai/wp-content/themes/layer6ai/assets/images/logo.svg</job_img><apply_email>careers@layer6.ai</apply_email><company>layer6</company><company_url>https://layer6.ai/</company_url><city>MaRS Discovery District at University &amp; College in Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Machine Learning Scientist</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__inner"&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__intro"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer 6 is a &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;leading&lt;/span&gt; machine learning research company, developing &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;advanced deep learning systems&lt;/span&gt; that have the power to uplift large populations while &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;advancing the field &lt;/span&gt;of artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our research is supported by access to &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;massive datasets&lt;/span&gt;, close collaboration with world renowned academic faculty, and a uniquely scalable machine learning platform. Research areas include deep learning, computer vision, time series analysis, natural language processing and recommendation systems etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our technical capabilities have been &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;publicly recognized&lt;/span&gt; through a number of wins in various international machine learning competitions, including the prestigious ACM RecSys Challenge (the only repeat winner in 2017 and 2018 and runner-up in 2019), Google&#8217;s Landmark Retrieval Challenge (2nd place in 2018, 3rd place in 2019), Kaggle: RSNA Pneumonia Detection Challenge (4th place in 2018) and the Stanford Question Answering Dataset (2nd place in 2019).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layer 6 was founded in Toronto in 2016 and backed by some of the most successful technology entrepreneurs in Canada. Layer 6 was acquired by TD Bank Group in 2018 and we continue being based in Toronto&#8217;s Discovery District &#8211; &lt;span class="highlight highlight__cyan"&gt;MaRS Centre&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="singleJobModal__main"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;As a machine learning scientist, you will&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join a world-class team of machine learning researchers with an extensive track record in both academia and industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research, develop, and apply new techniques in the intersection of deep learning and personalization to further advance our industry leading product.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with diverse real-life datasets that range from banking transactions, to predictive health applications, to audio/video consumption.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate closely with the engineering team in a fast paced startup environment and see your research deployed in production with very short turnaround.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Required&lt;/span&gt; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;PhD degree in Computer Science, Statistics, Operations Research, Mathematics or related field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong background in machine learning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of research experience with publication record&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of applying machine learning to solve real-world problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Preferred&lt;/span&gt; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with deep learning and/or collaborative filtering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience in software systems development and SaaS applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with one or more Java, Matlab, Scala, Tensorflow and MXNet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience using GPUs for accelerated deep learning training&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with AWS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span class="highlight highlight__yellow"&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial and inclusive culture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent health coverage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Four weeks paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Catered lunches twice a week over machine learning talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to collaborate with faculty at the Vector Institute&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://layer6.ai/careers/#Machine-Learning-Scientist-183</url><job_img>https://layer6.ai/wp-content/themes/layer6ai/assets/images/logo.svg</job_img><apply_email>careers@layer6.ai</apply_email><company>layer6</company><company_url>https://layer6.ai/</company_url><city>MaRS Discovery District at University &amp; College in Toronto</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Cloud Engineer</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. CanvassAnalytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp;teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Our infrastructure is based on Kubernetes and various Azure cloud technologies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We use CircleCI to continuously integrate and deploy code changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Deployment to production is git-based and happens on a regular basis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We use a micro services architecture built predominantly withPython&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Weve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kube flow to orchestrate our machine learning pipeline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; A passion for building secure and scalable cloud infrastructure inAzure, AWS or GCP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Experience creating and managing Kubernetes clusters, using tools such as Helm and Terraform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Strong networking and Linux knowledge, including knowing what to look for when things go wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Proven track record of proactive system management and monitoring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; An understanding of micro service architecture and distributed system design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Comfortable working with Python and Javascript&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Bonus points for managing Kafka and/or Spark clusters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, were looking for engineers&#160;that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Activation &amp;amp; Engagement&#160;Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration&#160;Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with DevOps, ProductDevelopment and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Excellence &amp;amp; Craft&#160;Cloud infrastructure is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Communication &amp;amp; Leadership&#160;An engineer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates.Were looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days&#160; to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160; From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes.&#160; We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160; We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/cloud-engineer</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Customer Success Manager</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day-to-day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we continue to scale rapidly and grow our customer base, Canvass Analytics has an exciting opportunity for aCustomer Success Manager. This role will be solely dedicated to overseeing the happiness of our clients. This includes ensuring successful engagement with our product, increasing product utilization based on customers business needs and ultimately deepening our relationship with the customer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may be an experienced CSM or have a background in successful project management and client delivery, and ultimately you get tech. You have several years experience working for or with industrial companies. You understand the processes and inter-working of a manufacturer. Ideally, you have an Engineering Degree as well as your PMICertification. Your persuasive nature and business acumen will be used to continually help our customers realize the many benefits of our software platform for improving and optimizing their assets and processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have an obvious passion for client happiness, delivery and engagement. You know best practices, processes, and methodologies and you understand technologies and systems to help get the job done. You know how to make conversations happen, how to anticipate issues(and proactively solve them) and understand how you can help. You move fast and readily adapt to change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have done this before for several years and you are chomping at the bit to do it again, yet better. You are excited at the opportunity to be the frontline person for our clients. You know that every project is an opportunity to grow Canvass presence with the customer and you love building the trusted relationships to help see our customers succeed. You want to build out the structure and the processes while rapidly reacting and responding to the needs of the customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Heres what our new Customer Success Manager will do:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Take care of our customers. Our customers are one of our most valuable assets. You will act as the main point of contact and trusted advisor to customers, managing the end-to-end process and nurturing the relationship:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oOwn, build and grow customer relationships with key client contacts at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oProactively identify problems and issues, solving them in innovative ways that result in exceptional levels of customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oOnboard and assist in training new customers and partners. &#160;Get them engaged and using the Canvass platform quickly. Help them increase their confidence to find solutions and opportunities for their company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oOwn the process for the initial platform deployment, coordinating all efforts with the client&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oDefine deployment architecture for customers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oWork with the Engineering andProduct team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oCollaborate across teams internally to troubleshoot issues, address concerns and answer questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oMaintain daily, weekly or monthly touch points depending on the stage of the project to increase product footprint and strengthen customer loyalty (while monitoring for red flags.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Whatever it takes. Identify gaps and address them. Introduce ideas and implement them. This is a build-as-you-go role. Its a challenge and its rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Be a trusted advisor to our leadership team. Advise and execute on customer engagement strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Continuously evolve. Create an approach that capitalizes on everything that we can offer to our clients and adapt so we can scale effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company thats at the forefront of leading-edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, and building a world class organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days&#160; to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160; From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes.&#160; We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160; We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/customer-success-manager</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Machine Learning Engineer</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. CanvassAnalytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We dont build machine learning pipelines to solve specific problems: we create pipelines that are able to solve classes of industrial data problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We use Keras, SciKit-Learn,XGBoost, SHAP and regularly research and add new libraries to our stack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Our pipelines and micro services are developed predominantly with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We use Kubeflow to build flexible ML pipelines and Kafka for data pipelines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; We use CircleCI to continuously test, integrate and deploy code changes, including ML&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Experience applying machine learning and deep learning algorithms to time-series problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Strong knowledge of probability and statistics, plus a passion for working with data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; The ability to implement feature engineering and data transformations at scale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Solid Python development skills, including experience with NumPy, Pandas and one or more ML libraries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; An understanding of micro service architecture and containerization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; A proven track record of delivering well-designed and tested software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, were looking for engineers&#160;that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Activation &amp;amp; Engagement&#160;Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration&#160;Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with DevOps, ProductDevelopment and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Excellence &amp;amp; Craft&#160;Cloud infrastructure is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Communication &amp;amp; Leadership&#160;An engineer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates.Were looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days&#160; to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&#160;&#160;&#160; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/machine-learning-engineer</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Product Designer</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our cloud-based web application puts process engineers in control of a scalable machine learning platform which enables them to improve factory operations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We work in small, cross-functional product teams composed of Product Designer, Product Manager and 2-4 developers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our modern, single-page-app is built in React. We follow a dual track agile methodology and release to production frequently&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We dont work from a feature roadmap: instead each team works towards a set of business objectives and is empowered to design and implement the best solution they can come up with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a data-driven culture and use leading edge tools that give us access to how users are interacting with our platform &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3+ years in software product design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A track record of working with product teams to create experiences that users love &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A portfolio that demonstrates a profound understanding of user problems and the ability to deduce elegant solutions out of complexity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An ability to present dense information in a way that is both engaging and informative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A solid background in both interaction design and visual design &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiarity with a variety of prototyping and testing techniques, and an expert at knowing which to use when &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication skills, able to work equally well with our customers, developers and internal stakeholders such as Marketing and Customer Success &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with tools like Figma, Sketch and InVision and an ability to identify the right UX tool and method for the job &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bonus Points for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferably youve worked in a startup before and understand life in a small company &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Empathy for manufacturers and process engineers &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Passion for how things are made and manufactured &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in B2B SaaS &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiarity with AI, data science and/or analytics &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience using Pendo &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are a young company and place great emphasis on the value and contribution that each person brings to the team. That also means that we are all called upon to bring multiple skills to our role. This is particularly true for this role as we are looking for someone to bring design thinking and a full spectrum of skills to Canvass. If you are looking to have a tight focus on just user research, or only spend your time designing screens this is not the role for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Development and ongoing ownership of user personas &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working closely with product managers and engineers to drive the product forward &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing mockups, wireframes and prototypes (low and high fidelity) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collect user insight and feedback and apply it throughout all phases of design by leading user research, interviews and usability testing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contribute to and advance our design system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/product-designer</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Product Manager</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our cloud-based web application puts process engineers in control of a scalable machine learning platform which enables them to improve factory operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We work in small, cross-functional product teams composed of Product Designer, Product Manager and 2-4 developers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We dont work from a feature roadmap: instead each team works towards a set of business objectives and is empowered to design and implement the best solution they can come up with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a data-driven culture and use leading edge tools that give us access to how users are interacting with our platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ years product management experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience working with a high growth B2B SaaS company&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication skills, able to work equally well with our customers, developers and internal stakeholders such as Marketing and Customer Success&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong data literacy and a track record of using data and experimentation to drive product decision&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A curious nature that think outside the box and love to experiment. &#160; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience working in an agile software development environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collaboration skills and the knowledge that success as a product manager is rooted in ensuring the whole team is aligned and working together toward the same goal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bonus Points for&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferably youve worked in a start up before and understand life in a small company&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Product Management experience in any of the following areas: Industrial, Oil and Gas, Metals, Mining, Food and Agriculture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Passion for how things are made and manufactured&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiarity with AI, data science and/or analytics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience using Pendo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Executing product strategy, road mapping, and prioritization of tasks related to driving the core customer experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding the context of our customers and users, and identifying the most important problems to solve to make them wildly successful&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigating and analyzing competitors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working with designers and engineers to drive the product forward, taking cues from and relaying information and feedback from users to the rest of the company&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continually collecting information and data from user behaviour to inform product direction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communicating roadmaps and metrics clearly to cross-functional teams to ensure quality collaboration on actionable items&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working with other departments to ensure they are positioned to succeed with the product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company thats at the forefront of leading-edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, and building a world class organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/product-manager</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Account Executive</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who We Need&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is seeking an Account Executive to join our sales team, a true hunter who wants to join us in North America at this pivotal point in our growth. You will develop your territory, build out the sales strategy and satisfy your drive to close the deal. You are a pioneer in an industry calling out for disruption, transforming the way operational decisions in the Industrial sector are made using AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who You Are&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are ready to take the next step in your career, understand the Industrial market and come with a roster of contacts who you are prepared to call. You have a proven track record of building relationships, from C-suite to Operations Managers. Empowering prospects and clients with data-driven insights to help them save money, accelerate competitive advantage and stay ahead is what motivates you. You are happiest on the road pursuing your targets and gaining new ground in this race to become an industry leader in industrial AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What You Bring&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have an Engineering degree and the logical, technical approach that comes with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Industry experience. You have 5 years selling into industrial companies, perhaps working for larger companies and moving into progressively more nimble ones. You get an adrenaline rush every time you close the deal. Your achievements go beyond quotas, extending into highly satisfied clients who trust your expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Motivation and drive. You get a thrill from pursuing the close which also means you are calm under pressure and can make sound decisions quickly. The confidence in our product and our company just makes it easier for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sales methodology and innovation. You believe in following a process because it works and changing it up when it doesnt. You want to contribute to building tactics and refining our processes for repeatable success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication. You have outstanding presentation skills. Your consulting approach in meetings gains the trust of those listening to you. Your written and verbal one-on-one communication skills - including the ability to listen and provide a real solution to a clients unique issues - are why you consistently exceed quota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Passion. You want to be in sales - this is where your career path starts and ends. You are genuinely interested in new ideas and new technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days &#160;to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160; From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes.&#160; We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160; We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/account-executive</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Team Lead, DevOps/Cloud </job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our platform is fully hosted in Azure and is primarily built using Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use CircleCI to continuously integrate and deploy changes using infrastructure-as-Code (IaC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our microservices architecture and tooling are developed in Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kubeflow to orchestrate our machine learning jobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Track record of building and managing secure, scalable, IaC-based infrastructure in Azure, AWS, or GCP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A passion for observability and automation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demonstrated leadership and mentoring skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience creating and managing Kubernetes clusters, using tools such as Helm and Terraform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong networking and Linux knowledge, including knowing what to look for when things go wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An understanding of microservice architecture and distributed system design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proficiency with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a senior role, requiring at least 8 years professional experience in related technical roles (e.g. DevOps, system administration, software development, testing)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were looking for a hands-on leader to manage and scale our growing cloud infrastructure and the team that supports it. A typical week will include a healthy mix of design, technical implementation, proactive production support and team management  perfect for someone who wants to stay close to the technology but still wants to flex their leadership skills. Reporting to the head of Engineering, you\'ll have full ownership of the resources that power our industrial AI platform as well as the DevOps tooling that makes it easy for development teams to bring their code into production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your teams responsibilities will include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High Availability - maximizing our uptime through design, automation and process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scalability  designing flexible infrastructure to meet the demands of high-burst, resource-intensive machine learning workloads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security  continuously improving our security and putting the technology in place to support SOC2 certification&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growth  starting as a team of two, help us grow by providing mentorship, expanding the teams capabilities and bringing new team members on board as our customer base expands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, were looking for engineers that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activation &amp;amp; Engagement Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with Product Development and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellence &amp;amp; Craft Operations is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication &amp;amp; Leadership Were looking for people who can teach and introduce their teammates to new concepts, and who can explain and contextualize their work to colleagues outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company thats at the forefront of leading-edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, that gives you room to grow and recognition. You will reap the rewards of your efforts with great incentive targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/team-lead-devops-cloud</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Test Automation Developer</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; We use a microservices architecture built predominantly with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our single-page web application is built with React&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use Kubernetes to manage our cloud deployments in Azure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kubeflow to orchestrate our machine learning pipeline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use CircleCI to continuously integrate, test and deploy code changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What were looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Were looking for candidates with:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Passionate about creating automated tests to ensure that an application works both before, during and post-deployment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested in applying their test automation knowledge to a platform offering multiple test challenges: IoT data ingestion, data pipelines, machine learning pipelines and of course an SPA front end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with the testing tools we already use (pytest, jest, cypress) and ready to add new ones into the mix&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid Python and Javascript programming skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An understanding of RESTful APIs and microservice architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, were looking for developers that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activation &amp;amp; Engagement Our developers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our developers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. Developers work very closely with a small number of other developers, a designer, and a product manager to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellence &amp;amp; Craft Software development is more than checking features off a list of requirements. We need our developers to build systems that are accessible to new teammates and extensible so that they can evolve with our business. We want our developers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication &amp;amp; Leadership A developer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates. Were looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and its getting noticed everywhere.&#160; Weve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by GooglesGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&#160;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&#160;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you dont have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&#160;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&#160;or&#160;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&#160;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/test-automation-developer</url><job_img>https://global-uploads.webflow.com/6047c01673f666512c81fabf/6048272db932b9fa32c1f6f2_Canvass%20Logo%20RGB%20(1).png</job_img><apply_email>info@canvass.io</apply_email><company>CANVASS</company><company_url>https://www.canvass.io/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario, Canada</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job><job><job_title>Senior AI Software Developer</job_title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ResAts__card-content"&gt;\n&lt;div class="row"&gt;\n&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a Vector Senior AI Software Developer, you will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #0e101a;"&gt;provide technical leadership&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span&gt;contribute to developing and integrating reusable software to apply and scale research breakthroughs in machine learning and AI. You will collaborate with some of the best and brightest machine learning and AI researchers and provide guidance to AI Software Developers and data scientists and researchers at industry sponsors and healthcare institutions to apply AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Provide technical leadership for applied research projects and AI/ML software development and integration projects following an agile methodology with teams that can include Vector AI developers, professional staff, researchers, industry sponsors and healthcare partners;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Design and lead development of reference applications and model templates that apply AI research to real-world problems using public and private data sets, providing software for training, testing, operating, and updating models;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Design and lead development of open source software for applying AI research techniques to common problems;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Mentor industry sponsors and healthcare partners on industry projects that apply AI research to shared problems, mentoring on engineering best practices, and assisting with operational issues;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Mentor researchers and AI software developers on software engineering and data science best practices;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Lead the development of prototypes and proofs of concept;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Report and present on software development including status and results; and,&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or related discipline; MSc/MEng preferred.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Minimum of four years of experience in industry applying machine learning for data science or technology product development or equivalent; experience across industries considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience as a technical lead for teams applying machine learning.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in applying machine learning to problems deployed in production.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in working closely with software engineers, data scientists and operations staff.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Demonstrated experience developing software that is deployed in production.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in data engineering working with messy real-world data.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in operational considerations for deployment of deep learning.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated analytical skills to identify signal in data and feasibility of prediction.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge and experience with Python.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Experience in popular open source deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, and CUDA).&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Experience with parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning algorithms.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;User interaction/design expertise with Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) engineering considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Kailyn Burke, HR Generalist, &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;using the link provided&lt;/span&gt;. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;January 10, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;The Vector Institute is committed to employment equity and diversity in the workplace and welcomes applications from women, racialized persons/visible minorities, Indigenous peoples, persons with disabilities, and LGBTQ+ persons. All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&#160;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Further, we are committed to fostering an environment of inclusivity and accessibility. If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="hr@vectorinstitute.ai%20" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;/div&gt;\n&lt;/div&gt;\n&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=115</url><job_img>https://images3.bamboohr.com/93316/logos/cropped.jpg?v=29</job_img><apply_email>hr@vectorinstitute.ai</apply_email><company>Vector Institute</company><company_url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/</company_url><city>Toronto, Ontario</city><location>Canada</location><reference /></job></jobs>